efunda.com 2019-12-15

# eFunda Privacy Notice

| • Materials  
---  
• Design Center  
• Processes  
• Units & Constants  
• Formulas  
• Mathematics  
  
---  

| 

---|---|---|---|---|---  
---  

**eFunda's Privacy Policy**  
  
---  
When registering with eFunda, you are assured that we would never willfully share your personal information with any third-party without your permission. We understand the trust you have put in us and we pledge to honor it. 

**How Do We Use Your Personal Information?**  
  
---  
  
As a partially free website, eFunda needs to derive its revenue from advertising and other partnerships. Members' personal information is aggregated and statistics are provided to advertisers and partners so they can realize the quantity and quality of our audience and choose eFunda as a key advertising channel. 

  eFunda's website uses temporary cookies to track your login status every time you visit us. We also use two cookies to remember your username and password if you selected the option on the login page. You can disable this feature at any time by unchecking the option to remove these cookies after you login. 

**Third Party Advertising**  
  
---  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website www.efunda.com. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. 

In particular: 

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. 
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. 
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 
  * To opt out from other advertisers, please use our [NAI Consumer Opt Out Form](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1).
